<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.ktexteditorpreviewplugin</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LGPL-2.1+</project_license>
  <name>KTextEditor Document Preview Plugin</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Connector de vista prèvia de documents del KTextEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Plug-in voor voorbeeld van KTextEditor document</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">'Plugin' de Antevisão de Documentos do KTextEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Plugin náhľadu dokumentu KTextEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">KTextEditor-insticksprogram för dokumentförhandsgranskning</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Додаток попереднього перегляду документа KTextEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKTextEditor Document Preview Pluginxx</name>
  <summary>Live preview of edited text documents in the target format</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Vista prèvia en viu de documents de text editats en el format de destí.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Live voorbeeld van bewerkte tekstdocumenten in het doelformaat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Antevisão em directo dos documentos de texto editados no formato-alvo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Direkt förhandsgranskning av redigerade textdokument i målformatet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Інтерактивний перегляд редагованих текстових документів у форматі призначення</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxLive preview of edited text documents in the target formatxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>This plugin for KTextEditor-based software (like the editor Kate or the IDE KDevelop) enables a live preview of the currently edited text document in the target format.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Aquest connector pel programari basat en el KTextEditor (com l'editor Kate o l'IDE KDevelop) habilita una vista prèvia en viu del document de text editat actualment en el format de destí.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Deze plug-in voor op KTextEditor gebaseerde software (zoals de editor Kate of de IDE KDevelop) schakelt een live voorbeeld in van het nu bewerkte tekstdocument in het doelformaat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Este 'plugin' para as aplicações baseadas no KTextEditor (como o editor Kate ou o IDE KDevelop) permite uma antevisão em directo do documento de texto editado de momento no formato-alvo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Det här insticksprogrammet för KTextEditor-baserad programvara (som editorn Kate eller den grafiska utvecklingsmiljön KDevelop) möjliggör en direkt förhandsgranskning  i målformatet av textdokumentet som för närvarande redigeras.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Це додаток для програмного забезпечення на основі KTextEditor (зокрема редактора Kate або комплексного середовища для розробки KDevelop) уможливлює інтерактивний перегляд поточного редагованого текстового документа у форматі призначення.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThis plugin for KTextEditor-based software (like the editor Kate or the IDE KDevelop) enables a live preview of the currently edited text document in the target format.xx</p>
    <p>For the display it uses the KParts plugin which is currently selected as the preferred one for the MIME type of the document.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Per a la visualització s'usa el connector KParts que actualment se selecciona com el preferit segons el tipus MIME del document.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Voor het tonen gebruikt het de KParts-plug-in die nu is geselecteerd als de geprefereerde voor het MIME-type van het document.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Para a visualização, ele usa o 'plugin' do KParts que está seleccionado de momento como o preferido para o tipo MIME do documento.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">För att visa den används KParts-insticksprogrammet som för tillfället är valt som det önskade för dokumentets Mime-typ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Для показу даних використовується додаток KParts, який визначено як бажаний для типу MIME документа.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFor the display it uses the KParts plugin which is currently selected as the preferred one for the MIME type of the document.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://cgit.kde.org/ktexteditorpreviewplugin.git/about/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kate&amp;component=plugin-preview</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=ktexteditorpreviewplugin</url>
  <update_contact>kossebau_at_kde.org</update_contact>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
</component>
